cncexotics.com 2016-08-28

# CNC Motors Inc. Serving Ontario, CA, New, Used Cars - Privacy Policy

|  |  |  What does CNC Motors Inc. (referred to herein as “CNC Motors Inc.”, the “Company,” “we,” “us” or “our”), do with your personal information?   
---|---  
| **Why?** | 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal and state law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
---|---  
| **What?** | 

The types of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we and/or our Partners collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Contact information, such as name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number
  * Date of Birth
  * Social Security number
  * Income and financial account information, such as account balances, payment history, and credit history
  * Payment and identify verification information, such as credit card number, social security number or comparable national identifiers, and driver’s license number 
  * Employment information
  * Unique identifiers, such as a customer number held in a cookie, an Internet Protocol (IP) address, a processor or device serial number, or other unique identifiers 
  * Your location coordinates (longitude, latitude, and radius)

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your Personal Information as described in this notice. In addition to collecting Personal Information, the Company and/or our Partners may use a variety of technologies that automatically collect General Information, which does not identify you personally. The types of General Information the Company and/or our Partners collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Cookies
  * Embedded Scripts
  * Web Beacons

---|---  
| **How?** | 

All financial companies need to share customers’ Personal Information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customer’s Personal Information; the reasons CNC Motors Inc. chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
---|---  
| 

**Reasons we can share your  
Personal Information with our Partners**

| 

**Does CNC Motors Inc. Share?**

| 

**Can you limit  
this sharing?**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purposes-**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| **YES** | **NO**  
  
**For our marketing purposes-**  
to offer our products and services to you

| **YES** | **NO**  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| **YES** | **NO**  
  
**For our affiliates to market to you-**   
information about your transactions and experiences

| **NO** | **WE DON’T SHARE**  
  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes-**  
information about your creditworthiness

| **NO** | **WE DON’T SHARE**  
  
**For our nonaffiliates to market to you**

| **NO** | **WE DON’T SHARE**  
| **To limit our sharing** | 

Email us at: [Frasercnc@aol.com](mailto:Frasercnc@aol.com)

**Please note:**

If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your Personal Information [30] days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
  
---|---  
**Questions?** | 

**Call 951-212-9581**  
  
|   
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| 

This notice is being provided by CNC Motors Inc. and our Partners.  
  
**How does CNC Motors Inc. protect my Personal Information?**

| 

To protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does CNC Motors Inc. collect my Personal Information?**

| 

The Company and our Partners may collect your Personal Information, for example, when you

  * Apply for financing
  * Apply for a lease
  * Provide employment history
  * Give us your contact information
  * Show your driver’s license
  * Interact with us through the Company’s website

The Company and our Partners may also collect your Personal Information from other third parties, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, non-affiliates, or other companies. The Personal Information you allow the Company and our Partners to access varies by source, and it is affected by the privacy policies established by those third parties. This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose Personal Information to the Company and/or our Partners. For more information about how those third parties handle your Personal Information, please refer to their privacy policies.  
  
**Do Not Track**

| 

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers that allows them to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. When a user activates DNT, the browser sends a message requesting that the website or online service not track the user. At the present time, standard DNT technology is not yet finalized and not all browsers support DNT; therefore, the Company does not recognize DNT signals. Instead, information collection and disclosure practices and the choices that the Company provides to users will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a DNT signal is received.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * Affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
**California Residents**

| 

Residents of the State of California may request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about the Personal Information (if any) we have disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:  
4980 Vanderbilt StreetCALIFORNIA  
Ontario, CA 91761  
For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, e-mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information or postage.  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.  
  
**Joint Marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.  
Our joint marketing partners may include the manufacturer affiliated lenders or other lenders.  
  
**Nonaffiliates** | 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Nonaffiliates we share with can include financial service providers (such as credit bureaus, manufacturer affiliated lenders, or other lenders), or they may be non-financial companies such as marketing companies or service providers. 

**Partner**

| 

Any person or entity with whom the Company enters into any kind of business transaction who is under an obligation to us to use reasonable care to keep Personal Information confidential, which may include our affiliates, nonaffiliates, and those with whom we joint market.  
  
Other important information regarding changes to this Privacy Policy  
  
**

The Company reserves the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes in practices and service offerings. If the Company modifies this Privacy Policy, the Company will update the “Effective Date” and such changes will be effective upon posting. Your continued use of the Company’s website following such material changes requires your affirmative consent to the changes. If you do not agree to the changes, your sole remedy is to cease using the Company’s products, services, and website. It is your responsibility to periodically check and review this Privacy Policy for changes.

**  
  
**DATE LAST MODIFIED: March 25, 2014**
